Martin P. Catherwood Library Administrative Office Additional Files /4219
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Administrative Office Additional Files
1981-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
/4219
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8055052
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Nicola Dardia, January 27, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Martin P. Catherwood Library.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
8055052
- SUNY Council of Library Directors Bolton Landing, NY, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  April 30 1997 - May 2 1997
- SUNY Council Library Directors, Bolton Landing, NY, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  May 1 - 3 1996
- SUNY Council of Library Directors, Bolton Landing, NY, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  April 26 - 28 1995
- SUNY Council of Library Directors, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  May 4 - 6 1994
- Bureau of National Affairs Named Space for John Stewart, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cornell Foundation House, Experiments in Distance Learning Dinner, New York, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  September 11 1997
- Dropkin Solicitation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Fall 1997
- Faculty Vita for 1995 TIIAP Submission (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Graduation Eve Dinner, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  March and December 1998
- Guide Information Resources on Employment Relations in US, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Law Firm Newsletter on the Web, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- National Center, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Kheel Party, New York, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  December 4 - 5 1997
- New York, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  October 31 1997
- New York, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  May 19 - 20 1997
- New York, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  April 14 - 16 1997
- New York, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  February 27 - 28 1997
- Partnerships for TIIAP Grant, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- TIIAP Advisory Council, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  March 1995
- Prospectus for Tip Grant, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Rochester Trip, Eugene Dorsey, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  June 30 1995
- Slavick, Monroe and Florence, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- TIIAP, Application Guidelines Part 1, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- TIIAP, Application Guidelines Part 2, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- TIIAP, Application Guidelines Part 3, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- TIIAP, Application Guidelines Part 4, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- TIIAP, Budget Narrative, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- TIIAP Budget Narrative and Statement of Matching and Operating Funds (Box 2, Folder 2)
- TIIAP Content, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- TIIAP Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- TIIAP Evaluation Model, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  April 1995
- TIIAP FAQ's, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- TIIAP Follow-Up, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- TIIAP Grant Application Submitted, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  April 19 1995
- TIIAP Grant Narrative, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  April 20 1995
- TIIAP Lessons Learned, Review Session in Washington, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  June 1996
- TIIAP Outreach Workshop, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- TIIAP Proposal as Submitted, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- TIIAP Project Narrative, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- TIIAP Prospectus (Box 2, Folder 14)
- TIIAP Timeline, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Varma, Madhurendra, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Video for Advisory Council, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  April 22 1994
- US Department of Labor Meeting, Washington, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  November 13 - 14 1996
- TIIAP, Washington, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  April 12 - 13 1995
- Workplace Policy Institute, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  December 1993
- Writers Guild and TIIAP Grant Application, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Library Acquisitions List, 1989-2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Library Catalog of the NYSSILR, Published by GK Hall, now Macmillan, 1966-1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Miller-McKersie Book, 1969-1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- J Gormly Miller Memorial Resolution Statement, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- SUNY Construction Fund (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Academic Assembly Presentation on Strategic Planning, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  September 20 1994
- Commercial Delivery of Journal Articles, Working Group Appointed by R Atkinson, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- University Librarian Search, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Comeniu (FMUK), 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Cornell Work and Environment Initiative, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ILR Associates, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ILR Press, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  February 14 1998
- Hygrothermograph Charts, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Segal Sculpture, Kheel Center, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  February 5 1998
- Sites for Conferences and Catering Services, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Academic Personnel Policy Committee Meetings, 1981-1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- AUL for Technology Search, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Grantsmanship Committee (McDonald, Chair), 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- ILR Dean Search: 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Law Library Committee, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- LMS Steering Committee, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Duplicate Monographs Study, Dankert/Blumen, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Krannert Materials Budget, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  December 1990
- Alliance for Public Technology, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Gopher, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Mirror Site for ILO, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Dunlop Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Screen Saver by Scott Nesmith, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Web Editorial Board, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Web/Gopher Services at ILR, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Hazard from Electrical and Magnetic Fields from Computer Equipment, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  August 27 1998
- ILR 729 Class Project to Assess Effect of Construction, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  December 1 1993
- Interim Renovations (1985 - 1992) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Job Meetings, Catherwood Building, SUCF, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New York: HBFR, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  August 18 1999
- Pre Fall 1993 Move Plan, 1993-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Academic Business Library Directors meeting, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Cornell, April 18 - 19 1999
- ASIS, Washington, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  November 2 - 6 1997
- ASIS, Chicago, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  October 8 - 12 1995
- ASIS, Columbus, Ohio, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- CIRL, Ann Arbor, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- CIRL, Wharton, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- CIRL, Michigan State, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- CIRL, Washington, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Future of Conflict Resolutions: Shaping the Cornell response, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  March 24 1998
- IRRA, Chicago, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  January 3 - 5 1998
- IRRA, Washington, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  January 6 - 8 1995
- IRRA Boston, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  January 3 - 5 1994
- Management Institute, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  May 28 - 30 1996
- Negotiation Workshop, R. Julian, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  12-8-1994
- Seminar on Information Services of the International Labor Organization (ILO), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  October 29 1996
- SLA Seattle, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  June 7 - 12 1997
- SLA, Boston, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  June 8 - 13 1996
- SUNY Council Library Directors: Bolton Landing, NY, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  April 22 - 24 1998
- SUNY Council Library Directors: Bolton Landing, NY, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)